Chandler! Chandler!
챈들러! 챈들러!
챈들러, 창문으로 내가 다 봤어
I saw what you were doing
in the window!
내 동생한테 하는 짓 봤으니까
당장 이리 나와
I saw what you're doing to my sister!
Get out here!
Listen, we had a good run.
그 동안 잘 피해 다녔어
얼마나 됐지?
4개월? 5개월?
What was it?
Four, five months?
That's more than most people
have in a lifetime. Goodbye.
남들 평생 한 거보다 나았어
그럼 잘 있어, 안녕
- 뭐하려고?
- 내빼는 거야
-What are you doing?
-I am going on the lam.
이리 와, 챈들러
Come on, Chandler.
I can handle Ross.
오빤 나한테 맡겨
Hold on!
잠깐만
Hey, Ross.
What's up, bro?
웬일이죠, 오라버니?
What the hell are you doing?
이게 대체 무슨 짓이야!
왜들 그래?
What's going on?
내 생각에는...
I think Ross knows
about me and Monica.
우리 로스한테 들켰나 봐
야, 옆에 있잖아
Dude, he's right there.
널 친구라고 생각했는데
얜 내 동생이라고
I thought you were my best friend!
This is my sister!
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot believe this!
둘도 없는 친구랑 동생이
어떻게 이럴 수가 있어!
그냥 놀아나는 게 아냐
난 모니카를 사랑해
We're not just messing around.
I love her.
네 동생을 사랑한다니까
I'm in love with her.
이런 식으로 알리게 돼서
정말 미안해
I'm so sorry that you
had to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I love him too.
어쨌든 사실이야
나도 챈들러 사랑해
My best friend and my sister!
내 가장 친한 친구랑 동생이?
믿어지지가 않아
I cannot believe this!
너희들도 와서 안아줘
굉장한 소식이잖아?
You guys want to probably
get some hugs in too. Big news!
됐어, 사실 우린 벌써
알고 있었거든
We've actually known for a while.
What? You guys knew?
뭐? 알고 있었어?
다 알면서 나한테만 숨겼다고?
You all knew and
you didn't tell me?
We were worried about you. We didn't
know how you were going to react.
널 생각해서 그런 거야
어떻게 나올지 몰라서
날 생각했구나
You were worried about me?
You didn't know how I'd react?
내가 어떻게 나올지 몰라서
그래, 잘됐다
Okay. All right.
얘들 사업 마저 끝내게
우리는 자리 비켜주자
Let's clear out of here and let
these lovebirds get back to business.
I'm just talking here.
He's the one doing your sister.
야, 난 잘못 없다?
네 동생 건드린 건 쟤야
The One With the Girl Who Hits Joey
You know what I just realized?
방금 생각난 건데
너희들이 아이를 낳으면...
If you guys have kids
뭐? 웬 아이?
We're having kids?
I call godfather!
대부는 내가 찜
그게 찜한다고 되는 거냐?
You can't just call godfather.
Shouldn't her brother be godfather?
그럼 외삼촌은 뭐야
Sure. If you cared enough
to call it first.
알았다, 찜도 안 한 게
얘들아, 너무 급하다
-You're a few steps ahead of us.
-Big zero gravity moon steps.
한마디로 뜬구름 잡는 거지
I just thought of
the greatest wedding gift.
오! 너희한테 줄
결혼선물 생각났다
I'll go in on that with you.
I couldn't decide.
그거 나랑 같이 하자
난 아무 생각도 안 나
그래
Hey, Katie.
어서 와, 케이티
This is Katie.
인사해, 케이티야
- 안녕하세요?
- 어서 와요
You ready to go?
그럼 나갈까?
- 화장실 다녀와서
- 그래, 저쪽이야
I'll run to the bathroom.
Where's lunch?
- 점심 어디서 먹을까?
- 중화요리는 어때?
I was thinking Chinese food.
중화요리 좋지
I love Chinese!
How did you know I love Chinese?
자기 눈치 한번 빠르다
She is so cute.
참 귀엽다
주머니에 쏙 들어가겠네
You could fit her
in your pocket.
She could fit in that little pocket
inside the pocket.
주머니 속의
주머니에도 들어가겠다
I don't know. I like her a lot,
and she's really nice, but....
글쎄, 나도 마음에 들어
정말 괜찮은 여자지만...
그런데 뭐?
But what?
날 자꾸 때리잖아
She keeps punching me.
In the cute, little
sweet way she just did?
방금 그 깜찍한 주먹질?
보기보다 강도가 훨씬 세
It's a lot harder than it looks.
진짜 아프다니까
She's hurting me.
너한테 필요한 게 있어
보디가드를 고용해라
I know what you need.
You need a bodyguard.
오빠, 벤 유치원
끝나면 시간 있지?
What is Ben doing after preschool?
왜들 이래
조이는 심각한데
Joey is having a problem.
A little girl is beating him up.
여자한테 맞고 다닌다잖아
조이, 이리 와봐
Joey, come here.
Honey, I know. This must be
really difficult for you, and
그래, 얼마나 괴롭겠니
I'm sorry, am I hurting you?
어머, 너무 세게 쥐었니?
- 어서 와
- 그래
집들이 선물 가져왔어
I brought you some housewarming gifts.
이건 소금
짭짤하게 잘살아
Salt, so your life always has flavor.
빵, 굶지 말라고
Bread, so you never go hungry.
그리고 향기 나는 욕실 양초
이유는 알지?
And a scented candle for the bathroom.
Because, well, you know.
고맙고 고마워
Thanks. Thanks.
And thanks, I guess.
- 이것도 감사
- 그래
- 안녕하세요
- 네
Welcome. I'm Steve Cera,
president of the tenants' committee.
입주 환영합니다, 세입자
모임 대표 스티브 세라예요
안녕하세요
로스 겔러입니다
Ross Geller.
And this is my friend Phoebe.
여긴 내 친구 피비
- 반가워요, 피비
- 저도요, 회장님
Mr. President.
I came to talk to you
about Howard.
하워드 얘기를 하러 왔어요
- 하워드?
- 네, 건물 관리인인데
He is the handyman
who's retiring next week.
다음주에 퇴직하게 돼서
100달러씩 걷기로 했어요
Everyone who lives here is kicking in
$100 as a kind of a thank you.
그 동안 수고해준 보답으로요
잘 생각하셨네요
That's nice.
어떻게, 수표로 하실래요?
Want to give me a check?
나중에라도 좋으니까
제 방 문 밑으로 넣어주세요
Not now. You can
slip it under my door.
아뇨, 그런 뜻이 아니라...
No, it's not that.
I just moved in.
전 방금 이사 왔는데요
그 분은 25년이나
여기서 일했답니다
Well, the guy's worked here
for 25 years.
하지만 전 여기 온 지
25분도 채 안 됐어요
Yes, but I've lived here
for 25 minutes.
네, 알겠습니다
Okay, I get it.
Wait! Look, I'm sorry, it's just
I've never even met Howard.
잠깐만요
죄송하지만 전
그 분을 뵌 적도 없어요
I mean, I don't know Howard.
하워드를 전혀 모른다구요
'관리인' 하워드라니깐요
Howard's the handyman.
Yes, but to me, he's just "man."
그래도 저한테는
하나의 '인간'일 뿐이죠
네, 알았어요
좋습니다
Okay. Fine. Whatever.
Welcome to the building.
겁나게 환영해부러요
이런 경우도 있나?
Can you believe that guy?
응, 저 안경 맘에 든다
I really like his glasses.
So then President Steve
told everyone I was a cheapskate...
그 회장이란 작자가 내가
자린고비라고 떠들어대서
이젠 전부 날 싫어해
...and now the whole building hates me.
A little kid spit on my knee.
어떤 꼬마는 내 다리에
침을 다 뱉더라
And told me to wipe it off
with my $100 bill.
100달러 짜리 지폐로 닦으래
뭘로든 닦아야겠다
You really should wipe it off
with something.
You know what?
계획이 있어
I'll throw a party.
For everyone in the building.
파티를 열 거야
건물 사람 다 초대해서
And I'll sit them all down and
explain that I am not a bad guy.
모두 앉혀놓고 설명하겠어
난 악당도 구두쇠도 아니고
I am not a cheap guy.
I'm just a guy...
단지 신념에 따라
행동하는 사람이라고
...who stands up
for what he believes in.
원칙이 있는 사람
A man with principles.
Sounds like a fun party.
그 파티 재미있겠다
이웃한테 호감을 사고 싶으면
그냥 100달러 내지 그래
If you want them to like you,
why don't you just pay the $100?
The party will cost you more.
- 파티 열면 비용이 더 들잖아
- 돈은 상관없어
That doesn't matter!
It's my principles!
We're talking about my principles!
이건 원칙의 문제야
지금 원칙 얘길 하는 거잖아
I thought it was about
your neighbors liking you.
난 이웃과의 관계가
중요한 줄 알았지
They'll like me once
they come to my awesome party.
날 좋아하게 될 거야
일단 내 광란의 파티에 와보면
그만 가볼게
명찰 만들 거야
I gotta get some nametags.
And that crazy party animal
will be your brother-in-law.
저 파티광이 장차
네 처남 될 사람이란다
그래, 재미는 있는데
Very funny.
But don't say that to Monica.
모니카 앞에선 그런 말하지 마
쓸데없는 생각하니까
Don't put any ideas in her head.
챈들러, 모니카는 벌써 그런
생각을 하고 있을지도 모르잖아
You do realize that those ideas
are probably already in Monica's head?
Why?
그건 왜?
Well, because she loves you
and because you love her.
걔는 널 사랑하고
넌 걔를 사랑하니까
그래서 뭐가 어쨌다고?
Yeah, so? What's
that supposed to mean?
챈들러, 그렇게 펄쩍 뛸 거 없어
너도 이미 알고 있던 거잖아
Don't freak out! I'm telling you
something you already know.
She left Richard because
he didn't want to have babies.
아기를 원치 않는다고
리처드랑도 헤어졌어
And she is a woman. And she's
almost 30. And, you know, it's Monica.
걔는 여자야
서른이 다 됐고...
모니카잖아
I don't see it that way.
I see two Monicas.
난 그런 식으로 생각 안 해
내가 아는 모니카는 둘이야
My friend who lives across
the hall and wants a lot of babies.
건너편에 사는 모니카는
아기를 엄청 좋아하지
또 다른 모니카는
내가 사랑하게 된 여자
And the new Monica
who I started to date.
모니카가 원하는 걸
누가 더 잘 알까?
Now, who is to say what she wants?
내가 맞아, 맞다고
I'm right.
그렇지 않아?
Am I right?
당연하지
Oh, absolutely.
난 리처드랑 달라
I'm completely different from Richard.
그 사람은 안과의사인데
난 안경 안 쓰거든
He's an eye doctor,
and I don't wear glasses.
You're right.
맞아, 네 말이 옳아
그럼 얘기가 전혀 다르지
You're absolutely right.
That makes everything different.
It's not different, is it?
사실은 전혀 안 다르지?
'다르다'의 뜻이
'똑같다'가 아니면
Not unless different
means "the same."
웃겨서 죽는 줄 알았어
자긴 진짜 돌았어!
You were so funny with that waiter.
You're such a nut!
막대빵 송곳니는
언제 해도 재미있어
You know, bread-stick fangs
are always funny.
자기가 해서 웃기는 거야
자기가 웃긴다니까!
No, you make them funny.
You're the funny one!
알았어
저기, 케이티
우리 얘기 좀 하자
Look, Katie.
Listen, we need to talk, okay?
Look, I like you.
I really do. I like you a lot.
난 자기가 좋아
정말이라니까
하지만 지금처럼
주먹질할 때면
But sometimes when you
playfully punch me like that...
...it feels like I'm being hit
with a very tiny but a very real bat!
아주 작은 몽둥이로
찜질 당하는 것 같아
그런다고 다칠까 봐?
Like I could hurt you.
Are you making fun of my size?
내가 작다고 놀리는 거지?
Don't make fun of me
because of my size!
그딴 식으로 놀리면 죽어!
Isn't this great?
정말 좋지?
Couldn't you just
stay like this forever?
영원히 이렇게 있으면 좋겠다
챈들러?
영원히 이렇게 있고 싶지?
Couldn't you just stay here forever?
그래, 이렇게든 저렇게든
아무렴 어때
Yeah, here, somewhere else.
You know, wherever.
- 너 괜찮아?
- 그럼, 난 좋아
Are you okay?
I'm cool.
아무 생각 없고
Casual.
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거야?
그냥 별 생각 없이 만나는
여자친구랑 놀고 있잖아
Just hanging out. Having fun
with the girl that I'm seeing casually.
Man, I knew it!
I knew you'd do this.
내가 이럴 줄 알았어
결국 이렇게 나오네
What?
뭐가?
다들 결혼이 어쩌고 하면서
놀려대니까 겁먹은 거잖아
Get all freaked out because
everybody was joking about marriage!
Well, you do want
all that stuff, right?
넌 그런 걸 원하지?
- 내가 뭘 원하는지 알아?
- 그래, 넌 아기를 원해
You know what I want?
Yes! You want babies!
You have baby fever!
아기라면 환장하지
누가 환장을 해
I do not have baby fever!
넌 아기와 결혼에
편집증이 있어
You're obsessed
with babies and marriage...
...and everything that's
related to babies and marriage.
그밖에도 많아
갓난애, 그리고 혼인...
좋은 생각이 있어, 압력솥
터지기 전에 불 끄자고
Why don't we turn the heat
down on this pressure cooker!
Have you lost your mind?
너 제정신이야?
문제는 내가 아니라 너야
쓸데없는 책임감 때문이라고
This isn't about me. This is about
you and your weird commitment crap!
천만에, 난 널 알아
네 머릿속이 훤히 보여
I know you. I know the thoughts
that you have in your head.
You don't know everything.
그렇게 잘 아셔?
Did you know I'm going out
with Rachel tonight instead of you?
오늘은 너 말고 레이첼이랑
외출한다는 사실도 아나?
여기서 애는 너밖에
없다는 사실도 아니?
And that the only baby here is you?
Did you know I can't even
look at you now?
지금 너 꼴도 보기
싫은 것도 알아?
I did not know that.
그건 몰랐다, 어쩔래
It'll be okay, right?
She won't leave me. This is fixable.
문제없어
날 버리진 않을 거야
잘 해결할 수 있어
-Yeah, sure.
-Absolutely.
- 그럼
- 당연하지
By me?
난 나야
- 안 되겠다
- 힘들겠어
뭔가 확실한 의사표시가
필요할 거 같다
Unless you make some big gesture.
Big, though.
그래, 확실하게
쉿! 마님이시다
The missus!
건터, 커피 한 잔만
Gunther, can I get a coffee?
To go.
가져갈게요
모니카...
I still don't want to talk to you.
아직 얘기할 기분 아냐
Tell me how to make things right.
내가 어떻게 하면 되겠니?
That's what we do.
뭐?
늘 그랬잖아
내가 잘못을 저질러도
I mess up, you tell me
how to fix it and I do.
네가 시키는 대로만 하면
다시 나 예뻐해 줬잖아
And then you think I'm cute again.
선생님 노릇도 이젠 지쳤어
I'm really tired of being
your relationship tutor.
Figure this out for yourself.
이번엔 혼자 답을 찾아봐
알았어?
If you're afraid
of a real relationship...
그리고 진지한 관계가 겁나면
아예 시작을 하지 마
...then don't be in one.
로스
닥터 겔러
- 하워드! 하워드!
- 하워드!...
Howard! Howard! Howard!
하워드! 하워드!
피비?
피비!
어머, 로스
Hi, Ross!
What are you doing here?
뭐하는 거야?
I thought this was your party,
and it's a party for Howard.
네 파티인 줄 알고 왔는데
하워드 송별회지 뭐야
He's the sweetest little man.
정말 귀여운 아저씨야
See you, Phoebe.
And thanks for chipping in.
또 봐요, 피비
참, 기부금 고마워요
별말씀을!
Oh, sure.
You chipped in?
돈을 냈어?
Yeah, $100.
그래, 100달러
I can't believe you gave him money.
피비, 돈을 주면 어떡해
I thought you agreed it was unreasonable
that they asked me for that money.
부당한 요구라는 거
너도 잘 알잖아
나한텐 달라고 한 적 없어
But they didn't ask me.
낯선 사람이 나타나서
돈을 턱 내놓으면 멋지잖아
I'm just the exotic, generous stranger.
That's always fun to be.
But you're making me look bad.
덕분에 난 더 나쁜 놈이 됐어
아냐, 이게 너한테도 좋아
No, I'm not! If anything,
I'm making you look better.
나 같은 거물이랑 어울리는
널 얼마나 부러워하겠니
They'll see you
talking to me. I'm a hit.
- 안녕, 피비
- 네
Hey, Phoebe!
아, 로스
Hey, Ross.
두 사람 아파트를 바꿔 봐요
피비가 우리랑 훨씬 잘 맞는데
Maybe you two could
switch apartments.
Because Phoebe is more
our kind of people.
Think about it.
잘 생각해보쇼
Okay, my bad.
그래, 내가 잘못했다
- 안녕
- 어서 와
와, 갑자기 몸이 불었네
You look big.
Thanks, I've been working out.
고마워, 운동 좀 했다
스웨터 여섯 벌
입은 거 티 나냐?
Listen, is it obvious
I'm wearing six sweaters?
그래
But it's not obvious why.
이유는 잘 모르겠지만
I'm breaking up with Katie,
so I put on some extra padding.
나 케이티랑 끝낼 거야
그래서 보호막을 댔지
If she hits me when she is happy,
can you imagine how hard she'll hit...
행복할 때 치는 게 그 정돈데
'조이의 사랑'을 끝낸다면
얼마나 무지막지하게 패겠냐
...when I take away the Joey love?
맞다, 그렇게 표현했었지
Oh, right. I forgot that you call it that.
케이티
어서 와
Hey, cute jacket.
케이티, 재킷 예쁘네요
Thanks.
고마워요
마음씨도 곱지
-That's so sweet!
-Ouch!
아야!
아야?
Did Joey tell you to say that?
You guys are too much!
조이가 시킨 거죠?
정말 너무하네요!
그게 아니죠, 내가 볼 때
너무한 사람은 케이티 같은데
You know what?
I gotta tell you...
...I think you're the one
that is too much.
조이는 참 좋은 친구를 뒀네요
Joey has the nicest friends.
And the nicest girlfriend.
여자친구도 괜찮고
정말 좋은 분이네요
You're so sweet!
댁이 더 좋아!
조이?
She just kicked me.
방금 날 찼어
Aren't you going to do something?
가만있을 거야?
빨리 어떻게든 해봐
나 저 문으로 나가기 전에
Do something or I'll walk
out that door right now.
어때? 할 거지?
Are you going to?
아뇨
피비?
내 말이 그 말이에요
피비, 피비!
This is a disaster.
Can't I please just go?
더 이상 못 참겠다
나 그냥 가면 안 돼?
안 돼, 너 띄우는 중이야
I'm talking you up to people.
조금만 기다려봐
긴장 풀고 뭐 좀 먹어
Give it some time, relax.
Get something to eat.
그래...
What did you tell them about me?
나에 대해 뭐라고 했는데?
너랑 에밀리 얘기했어
동정표 좀 얻을까 하고
I told them about you and Emily.
Trying to get some sympathy.
But you came off as the bad guy.
근데 결론은 네가
나쁜 놈이 돼버렸어
뭐?
말을 잘못했나 봐
I told it wrong.
We should talk about that because
I don't understand what happened there.
우리 그 얘기 좀 해보자
난 전혀 이해가 안 돼
와, 이 케이크 괜찮다
This cake is really good!
Things are looking up.
봐, 벌써 기분이 나아지잖아
Oh, my God!
Someone cut Howard's cake!
세상에, 누가 하워드의
케이크를 잘라먹었네
누가 이런 짓을 했죠?
Who would do a thing like that?
3B.
3B
공짜 음식도 먹었고
잔치 흥도 깼으니
You got your free food.
You ruined everyone's fun.
그만 가주시죠
Isn't it time you went home?
Go back to 3B, 3B.
3B로 돌아가요, 3B양반
여러분, 흥분하지 마세요
진정하고 제 말 들으세요
Everyone, calm down!
I have something that I'd like to say.
Who here likes Ross?
여기서 로스를 좋아하는 분?
물론 로스가 싫겠죠
Of course you don't like him.
He didn't give you any money.
내라는 돈도 안 내고
He raised his own hand
when I asked, "Who likes Ross?"
자기가 자기 좋다고
자기 손을 들지 않나
And he's wearing two nametags.
명찰도 두 개나 달고
사실 저도 로스를
처음 봤을 땐 싫었어요
I'll be honest. When I first met Ross,
I didn't like him at all.
하지만 친해지고 나니까
그렇게 자상하고 따뜻하고
Once I got to know him,
I saw that he is really sweet...
...and caring and very generous.
마음이 넓을 수가 없어요
잘 알지도 못하면서 함부로
사람을 판단하는 거 아니에요
All I'm saying is, don't judge
Ross before you get to know him.
전 지금 여러분이 좋지만
처음부터 그렇진 않았어요
You know, I like all of you guys now.
But when I first met you, you know?
예를 들어, 커트?
왕짜증 주정뱅이 같았어요
Kurt? I thought, abrasive drunk.
롤라?
대책 없는 팔푼이
Lola?
Mind-numbingly stupid.
그리고 두 사람
You guys. Gold digger,
cradle-robbing perv.
돈만 아는 속물
영계 밝히는 변태
So I think you all know what I mean.
어때요, 다들 이해하셨군요
Obviously, I didn't think
they would throw things.
물건을 집어던질 건 뭐니
내가 그 사람들 모욕할 때
네가 나서서 변호했으면
I thought if I kept insulting them
you'd defend them.
Then you'd look like the hero.
영웅이 되는 거잖아
와, 그래...
그렇게 심오한 뜻이?
See, I did not get that.
Where's Monica? I need
to talk to her, it's urgent.
모니카 어디 있어?
급한 일이야, 여기 있나?
전데요?
I'm Monica.
할 말이 있어, 급해
I need to talk to you. It's urgent.
말해봐
I've been thinking...
생각 많이 했어
...about us. A lot of "us" thinking.
우리 관계에 대해
진지하게 고민했다고
그런데 해결책은 하나밖에 없겠어
I guess there's
only one way to do this.
뭐야...
What are you doing?
너 지금 왜 이래?
- 모니카?
- 안 돼, 하지 마
Don't do it.
Will you marry me?
나랑 결혼해줄래?
What a bad idea.
- 맙소사
- 내가 돌겠다
차마 못 보겠다
I can't not look at it.
Why are you doing this?
- 챈들러, 왜 이러는 거야?
- 나도 몰라
I don't know.
But I know I'm not afraid to do this.
하지만 이제 두렵지 않아
챈들러...
I'm doing this because I'm sorry?
미안해서 이러는 걸까?
Do you think the best reason
to get married is because you're sorry?
결혼하려는 이유가
미안한 마음 때문이라고?
가장 큰 이유는 임신이지
The best reason is pregnancy.
Sorry is fourth, behind being ready
and actually wanting to get married.
미안한 맘은 네 번째쯤 될 거야
'준비됐다, 결혼하자' 다음이니까
Will you be my wife?
내 아내가 돼줄래?
챈들러, 잠깐 흥분 가라앉히고
이 우스꽝스런 상황을 돌아봐
I want you to take a minute and think
about how ridiculous this sounds.
I'm kind of wishing
everyone wasn't here now.
그러게, 쟤들 좀 치워줘
자기야
난 아무 말도 안 했어
None of that came from me.
I never said I wanted to have babies
and get married!
누가 당장 결혼해서
아기를 갖고 싶댔어?
혼자선 정리가 안 돼서
쟤들이랑 얘기했거든
I was really confused.
Then I talked to these guys.
Who? Two divorces and Joey?
두 번 이혼한 남자랑 조이?
- 야
- 쟤 말이 맞아
She's right, you know?
Yeah, but still, cheap shot!
그래도 좀 야비하다 야
들어봐
You know when I said
that I want you...
내가 이번 문제는 혼자서
해결해보라고 했지?
...to deal with relationship stuff
all on your own?
You're not ready.
넌 아직 안 되겠다
나도 그렇게 생각했어
I didn't think I was!
세상에
Oh, my God.
내가 좋다고 했으면
어쩌려고 그랬어?
What would you have done
if I had said yes?
I would've been happy because...
행복했겠지
사랑하는 여자와 여생을
함께 보낼 수 있으니까
...I would spend the rest of
my life with the woman I love.
Or you would have seen
a Chandler-shaped hole in that door.
아니면 저 문에 챈들러 모양의
구멍이 생겼을 거야
Will you pass that knife?
로스, 그 칼 좀 주라
No, I will not.
싫다면 어쩔래
됐다, 갑자기 웬 심통이야
You don't have to be mean about it.
그렇구나, 미안하다
나랑 결혼해줄래?
You're right. I'm sorry.
Will you marry me?
난 너한테 청혼할까봐
지난주에 인사를 안 했거든
I was going to ask you to marry me
because I didn't say hello to you.
그걸로는 동거밖에 안 될 걸?
난 잘 모르겠다, 챈들러?
Or ask them to move in with you.
But I'm not sure. Chandler?
대체 언제까지 이럴래?
How long is this going to go on?
I think the length of teasing...
놀림 받는 기간은
어느 정도의 바보짓을
했느냐에 달렸으니까
...is directly related to how insane
you were. So a long time.
꽤 오래갈 거야
This is fun!
이건 어때?
레이첼, 우리 재결합 깨진 거
다 내 잘못이야, 결혼해줄래?
Remember that
"we were on a break" thing?
I'm sorry.
Will you marry me?
That's not funny.
한 개도 안 웃겨